

GONZALO POZZI

DATA ANALYST Industrial Engineer - Msc. in Project Management

ABOUT ME

EDUCATION

Professional with excellent understanding and proficiency in the use of different platforms for effective data analysis. I am currently looking for job opportunities (preferably remotely) that allow me to refocus my career to be able to combine my passion for data with making impactful decisions that empower and drive the success of companies, by committing myself to add value from my skills, experiences, knowledge and training.

PORTFOLIO

More about my projects in:



www.gonzalopozzi.com.ar

CONTACT INFO.

+5492213041970



gonzalopozzi@gmail.com



in linkedin.com/in/gpozzi/



La Plata - Buenos Aires



ADDITIONAL STUDIES

Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate | Google - Coursera | 2021

Msc. in Project Management | Universitat de Barcelona | 2019: completed.

Industrial Engineering | Universidad Nacional de La Plata | 2017: completed.

Data Scientist | Acámica | 2021

Tableau Fundamentals Skill Track | Datacamp | 2021

Spreadsheets Fundamentals Skill Track | Datacamp | 2021

Creating Dashboards in Tableau | Datacamp | 2021

Data Manipulation With Pandas | Datacamp | 2021

Manipulating Time Series With Python | Datacamp | 2021

Time Series Analysis in Python | Datacamp | 2021

Streamlined Data Ingestion With Pandas | Datacamp | 2021

Writing Efficient Python Code | Datacamp | 2021

Managing Big Data With SQL | Duke University - Coursera | 2020

SOFT SKILLS

Proactivity Continous learning Attention to detail Methodical Analytic Team worker

SOFTWARE

MS Office

Word - Excel - Outlook - PowerPoint

Programming languages

Python - SQL

Other programming

Machine learning

Data wrangling in Python (Pandas- Numpy)

Data visualization in Python (Seaborn - Matplotlib)

Webscraping / automation (Selenium - BeautifulSoup)

Natural Language Processing (SpaCy)

Visualization

Tableau - PowerBI

IDIOMAS

Spanish | native

English | advanced - oral and written

Italian | A2 - Dante Alighieri - 2005

Portuguese | A1 - Escuela de Lenguas UNLP - 2015



PORTFOLIO

More about my projects in:



www.gonzalopozzi.com.ar

CONTACT INFO.

+5492213041970



gonzalopozzi@gmail.com



in linkedin.com/in/gpozzi/



La Plata - Buenos Aires



Argentina

SOFT SKILLS

Proactivity Continous learning Attention to detail Methodical Analytic Team worker

GONZALO POZZI

DATA ANALYST

Industrial Engineer - Msc. in Project Management

WORK EXPERIENCE

Alsedo Lorenzo e Hijos La Plata, Bs. As., Argentina.

CONTINOUS IMPROVEMENT ANALYST | DEC. 2019 - CURRENT

- Surveying, classification and parameterization of more than 3000 unique products for the design of the company's inventory system.
- Selection and implementation of the ERP for the digitization of company's processes, achieving a 30% reduction in the number of manhours allocated to administrative tasks and a traceability of all company sales
- Development of scripts in Python for the automation of tasks (synchronization of price lists to the ERP from Excel spreadsheets, downloading of sales records, loading of historical price records in database)
- Streamlining the process of issuing product price lists from more than 30 suppliers, which began to be issued and distributed weekly.

EDVSA - Río Gallegos, Argentina.

TECHNICAL OFFICE / ENGINEERING COORDINATOR | DEC. 2017 - JUN. 2018 PROJECT: PIAM - Plataform AM3 (Revamping offshore platform)

- Assistance in coordinating the tasks of 2 work fronts (day and night shifts, up to 6 supervisors and 75 operators per front).
- Coordination of transport operations, loading and unloading of materials.
- Survey of work progress on the field, monitoring and interim certification.
- Surveying engineering documentation to compute the certifiable quantities.
- Assistance in the assembly of quality and pre-commissioning data books.

OPERATIONS COORDINATOR | JUL. 2017 - DEC. 2017

PROJECT: PIAM - Plataform AM2 (Revamping offshore platform).

- Assistance in coordinating the tasks of 2 work fronts (day and night shifts, up to 4 supervisors and 40 operators per front).
- Daily reporting, detailing tasks done, personnel, and unproductive hours of 2 daily work fronts.
- Preparation and monitoring of interim certificates.
- Personnel logistics coordination.

JCR S.A. - SVSA Joint Venture - Buenos Aires, Argentina.

PROJECT PLANNER / CONTROLLER | JAN. 2017 - JUL. 2017

PROJECT: Gasoducto del Noreste Argentino (GNEA) - 280 km of 24" pipe laying 24" and corresponding surface facilities.

- Preparation of weekly progress reports for construction and management control.
- Control, monitoring and interim certification of the different construction phases of the project.
- Coordination with the project management team to solve project problems and ensure the execution of the different tasks.
- Supervision of contractual execution of subcontractors and suppliers.
- Root cause reporting to determine causes of delays in critical activities.



GONZALO POZZI

DATA ANALYST

Ing. Industrial - Máster en Project Management

PERFIL

Profesional con excelente comprensión y competencias en diferentes plataformas para un análisis de datos efectivo. Actualmente me encuentro en búsqueda de oportunidades laborales (preferentemente de manera remota) que me permitan poder darle un nuevo enfoque a mi carrera y así combinar mi pasión por los datos con la toma de decisiones impactantes que empoderen e impulsen el éxito de las empresas. Comprometiéndome a sumar valor a partir de mis competencias, experiencias, conocimientos y formación.

PORTFOLIO

Más sobre mis proyectos en:



www.gonzalopozzi.com.ar

CONTACTO - INF. PERS.

+5492213041970

gonzalopozzi@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/gpozzi/

La Plata - Buenos Aires

Argentina

COMPETENCIAS

Proactividad Aprendizaje continuo Atención al detalle Metodicidad Capacidad analítica Perfil resolutivo Trabajo en equipo Relaciones interpersonales

FORMACIÓN ACADÉMICA

Máster en Project Management | Universitat de Barcelona | 2019: graduado. Ingeniería Industrial | Universidad Nacional de La Plata | 2017: graduado.

FORMACIÓN COMPLEMENTARIA

Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate | Google - Coursera | 2021

Data Scientist | Acámica | 2021

Tableau Fundamentals Skill Track | Datacamp | 2021

Spreadsheets Fundamentals Skill Track | Datacamp | 2021

Creating Dashboards in Tableau | Datacamp | 2021

Data Manipulation With Pandas | Datacamp | 2021

Manipulating Time Series With Python | Datacamp | 2021

Time Series Analysis in Python | Datacamp | 2021

Streamlined Data Ingestion With Pandas | Datacamp | 2021

Writing Efficient Python Code | Datacamp | 2021

Managing Big Data With SQL | Duke University - Coursera | 2020

INFORMÁTICA

MS Office

Word - Excel - Outlook - PowerPoint

Lenguajes de programación

Python - SOL

Otros conocimientos de programación

Manipulación de datos en Python (Pandas- Numpy)

Visualización en Python (Seaborn - Matplotlib)

Webscraping / automatización (Selenium - BeautifulSoup)

Procesamiento de lenguaje natural (SpaCy)

Conocimientos en Machine Learning

Visualización de datos

Tableau - Power BI

IDIOMAS

Español | nativo

Inglés | avanzado - oral y escrito

Italiano | A2 - Dante Alighieri - 2005

Portugués | A1 - Escuela de Lenguas UNLP - 2015



PORTFOLIO

Más sobre mis provectos en:



www.gonzalopozzi.com.ar

CONTACTO - INF. PERS.

+5492213041970



gonzalopozzi@gmail.com



角 La Plata - Buenos Aires



Argentina

COMPETENCIAS

Proactividad Aprendizaje continuo Atención al detalle Metodicidad Capacidad analítica Perfil resolutivo Trabajo en equipo Relaciones interpersonales

GONZALO POZZI

DATA ANALYST

Ingeniero Industrial - Máster en Project Management

EXPERIENCIA LABORAL

Alsedo Lorenzo e Hijos La Plata, Bs. As., Argentina.

ANALISTA DE MEJORA CONTINUA | DIC. 2019 - ACTUALIDAD

- Relevamiento, clasificación y parametrización de más de 3000 productos únicos para el diseño del inventario de la empresa.
- Selección e implementación del sistema de gestión para la digitalización de procesos. logrando una reducción de 30% en la cantidad de horas hombre destinadas a tareas administrativas y una trazabilidad de la totalidad de las ventas de la empresa.
- Desarrollo de scripts en Python para la automatización de tareas (sincronización de listas de precios al ERP desde planillas Excel, descarga de registros de ventas, carga de registro histórico de precios en base de datos)
- Agilización del proceso de emisión de listas de precios de productos de más de 30 proveedores, las cuales pasaron a emitirse y distribuirse semanalmente.

EDVSA - Río Gallegos, Argentina.

COORDINADOR DE INGENIERÍA - OFICINA TÉCNICA | DIC. 2017 - JUN. 2018 PROYECTO: PIAM - Plataforma AM3 (Revamping plataforma offshore)

- Asistencia en la coordinación de tareas de 2 frentes de trabajo (turnos día y noche, hasta 6 supervisores y 75 operarios por frente).
- Coordinación de operaciones de transporte, carga y descarga de materiales.
- Relevamiento de avances de obra en campo, seguimiento y certificación.
- Relevamiento de la ingeniería de detalle para computar las cantidades certificables.
- Asistencia en el armado de data books de calidad y precomisionado.

COORDINADOR DE OPERACIONES | JUL. 2017 - DIC. 2017 PROYECTO: PIAM - Plataforma AM2 (Revamping plataforma offshore).

- Asistencia en la coordinación de tareas de 2 frentes de trabajo (turnos día y noche, hasta 4 supervisores y 40 operarios por frente).
- Reporte diario de tareas, detallando tareas, personal, y horas improductivas de 2 frentes de trabajo diarios.
- Confección y seguimiento de certificaciones de obra.
- Coordinación logística de personal.

UTE JCR S.A. - Servicios Vertúa - Capital Federal, Argentina.

PLANIFICACIÓN Y CONTROL DE OBRA I ENE. 2017 - JUL. 2017

PROYECTO: Gasoducto del Noreste Argentino (GNEA) - 280 km de tendido de cañería 24" e instalaciones correspondientes.

- Elaboración de informes de avance semanales de construcción y de control de gestión.
- Control, seguimiento y certificación de las distintas fases constructivas de provecto.
- Coordinación con el equipo de project management para resolver inconvenientes del proyecto y asegurar la ejecución de las distintas tareas.
- Supervisión de ejecución contractual de subcontratistas y proveedores.
- Redacción de informes para determinar causas de atrasos en actividades críticas.